<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lancaster Beer &amp; Code</title>
    <description>We are the Lancaster Beer &amp; Code collective. A group of  technologically-inclined friends who appreciate the finer things in life - beer and code.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 13:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 13:22:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>CoronaPhona</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;See: &lt;a href=&quot;https://lbandc.github.io/coronaphona&quot;&gt;lbandc.github.io/coronaphona&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using &lt;a href=&quot;https://twilio.com&quot;&gt;Twilio&lt;/a&gt;, we provide a simple, single helpline that vulnerable people in your community can call. This will seamlessly connect them to local volunteers in a round-robin manner, so they don’t have to call or remember a list of telephone numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;we-want-to-support-the-vulnerable-during-this-crisis&quot;&gt;We want to support the vulnerable during this crisis&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vulnerable in your community may not be digitally active - they may not know about Facebook groups, community volunteer groups or similar. For this reason we wanted to provide a single number that they can call to be connected to volunteers in their local area who might be able to help them in times of need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-it-works&quot;&gt;How it works&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You contact us to register your interest in being a volunteer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You provide a list of volunteers who are happy to be phoned&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We create a special community phone number for you, which when called, will ring around all the numbers you provided in random order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You create a leaflet with your custom phone number on it, and distribute it locally.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;get-involved&quot;&gt;Get involved&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can only do this with your help! If you are interested in helping the vulnerable in your community or you already know of a community volunteer group that would benefit from this, please get in touch with us via email at coronaphona@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 13:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/coronaphona/covid19/projects/2020/03/23/coronaphona.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/coronaphona/covid19/projects/2020/03/23/coronaphona.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>coronaphona</category>
        
        <category>covid19</category>
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
